If the sun burns out tonight
I wonder if the sun burnt out tonight
Would you let me go or hold me tight?
Just one touch could erase the light
Say we’ll be alright
Tell me you mean it
Make me believe it
I’m barely breathing
Help me kill the curse
It’s getting colder
Hell’s freezing over
So pull me closer
Hit me where it hurts
End of the world
All I need is you
If the sun burns out tonight
Supernova, all I see is you
Now the void calls out my name
It gets louder every day
And in the darkness all I need is you
If the sun burns out tonight
Hit me where it hurts
End of the world
All I need is you
If the sun burns out tonight
Supernova, all I see is you
Now the void calls out my name
It gets louder every day
And in the darkness all I need is you
If the sun burns out tonight
Cos the silence is deafening now
Only the sound of our hearts still beating
Please drag me out
Give me a reason to keep on breathing
The heavens open, the sky’s black and blue
The end’s approaching for me and you
We’ll survive, just you and I
If the sun burns out tonight